{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Theater \u0026 Audio Repair Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40309/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40309,"taskName":"Home Theater System or Media Center - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair or Service a Home Theater System or Media Center","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Theater \u0026 Audio Repair Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":130,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"A/V AV visual tv audio/visual","textMessagingName":"Repr Entertain Sys","rolloverLongDesc":"Repairs, adjusts, rearranges, reconnects existing audio visual equipment. Note separate categories for new installations \u0026 for full-blown home theaters.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes DVD, TV, VCR \u0026 home theater systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service a Home Theater System or Media Center.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Theater \u0026 Audio Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Home Theater System","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":46395,"bridgeTaskText":"Do you need a TV or other component repaired? ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"TV or Home Theater Accessory Repair","bridgeTaskLinkId":9212,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Home Entertainment System Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Home Theater System or Media Center - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Media Center Project","urlName":"Home-Theater-System-or-Media-Center-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Theater \u0026 Audio Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"A/V,AV,visual,tv,audio/visual,reapir,projectorscomputer,audiovisual,audio,Systems,Equipment,Entertainment","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":609,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40309/":{"taskOID":40309,"originalTaskOID":40309,"setID":609,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6340,"questionDisplayText":"Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of the problem:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20356,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Audio or video problems","answerDisplayText":"Audio or video problems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20357,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No HD picture","answerDisplayText":"No HD picture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"System won't power on","answerDisplayText":"System won't power on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20359,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remote not working correctly","answerDisplayText":"Remote not working correctly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20360,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Connection or integration problems","answerDisplayText":"Connection or integration problems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20361,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6341,"questionDisplayText":"Systems to repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What components are not working? ","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20362,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cables","answerDisplayText":"Cables","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20363,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"TV lift or dropdown","answerDisplayText":"TV lift or dropdown","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20364,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Media Server","answerDisplayText":"Media Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20365,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20366,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20367,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20368,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Surround Sound","answerDisplayText":"Surround Sound","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6340,"questionDisplayText":"Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of the problem:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20356,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Audio or video problems","answerDisplayText":"Audio or video problems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20357,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No HD picture","answerDisplayText":"No HD picture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"System won't power on","answerDisplayText":"System won't power on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20359,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remote not working correctly","answerDisplayText":"Remote not working correctly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20360,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Connection or integration problems","answerDisplayText":"Connection or integration problems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20361,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20356,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Audio or video problems","answerDisplayText":"Audio or video problems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20357,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No HD picture","answerDisplayText":"No HD picture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"System won't power on","answerDisplayText":"System won't power on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20359,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remote not working correctly","answerDisplayText":"Remote not working correctly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20360,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Connection or integration problems","answerDisplayText":"Connection or integration problems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20361,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6341,"questionDisplayText":"Systems to repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What components are not working? ","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20362,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cables","answerDisplayText":"Cables","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20363,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"TV lift or dropdown","answerDisplayText":"TV lift or dropdown","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20364,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Media Server","answerDisplayText":"Media Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20365,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20366,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20367,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20368,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Surround Sound","answerDisplayText":"Surround Sound","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20362,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cables","answerDisplayText":"Cables","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20363,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"TV lift or dropdown","answerDisplayText":"TV lift or dropdown","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20364,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Media Server","answerDisplayText":"Media Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20365,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20366,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20367,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20368,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Surround Sound","answerDisplayText":"Surround Sound","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}